cleartripforbusiness.com 2014-02-13

# Cleartrip Privacy Policy

By accessing this Site, certain information about you, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigation through the Site, the systems and programs used and the time spent, along with other similar information, may be stored on our servers. We may use this stored information with the objective of providing you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience.

Such stored information may not specifically identify you. However, we may use the same for web site traffic analysis or for other such purposes, as we may deem appropriate.

If you provide unique identifying information, such as name, address and other information to us, such information may be used for statistical and/or other purposes. If you choose to transact on the Website, we collect information about your buying behaviour as well.

Any personally identifiable information you submit while booking with Cleartrip will ONLY be disclosed to travel suppliers and affiliates who are linked to your bookings. We will not disclose or sell or in any way reveal your information to any other unrelated third party.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

We have implemented and use Display Advertising through Remarketing with Google Analytics. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager.](http://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/preferences/) Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

We want you to feel confident about using Cleartrip.com to plan and purchase your travel, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies.

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

All payments on the Website are Verisign SSL secured. This means all Personal Information you provide on the Website is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. The same process happens when you make travel purchases on the Website.

We respect your privacy and all the data provided by your shall be govered under the above Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use of Cleartrip, which may be amended from time to time
